Guide to the W. H. Taylor Collection, 1837-1938 JL007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- SERIES C. PURCHASING, RECEIVING, AND PRODUCTION RECORDS, 1870-1908
  - Orderbook, Aug-Dec 1880 (Box 196)
  - Orderbook, Dec 1880-Feb 1881 (Box 196)
  - Orderbook, Feb-April 1881 (Box 196)
  - Orderbook, June-Aug 1881 (Box 196)
  - Orderbook, Aug-Oct 1881 (Box 196)
  - Orderbook, March-May 1882 (Box 196)
  - Orderbook, May-July 1882 (Box 197)
  - Orderbook, Sept-Nov 1882 (Box 197)
  - Orderbook, Feb-May 1883 (Box 197)
  - Orderbook, July-Aug 1883 (Box 197)
  - Price book, n.d. (Box 197)
  - Order ledger, [1907-1912?] (Box 197a)
  - Sales book index, 1888-1889 (Box 198)
  - Sales book, 1888-1889 (Box 199)
  - Sales book index, 1889-1890 (Box 200)
  - Sales book, 1889-1890 (Box 201)
  - Sales book, 1890-1892 (Box 202)
  - Sales book index, 1892-1893 (Box 203)
  - Sales book, 1892-1893 (Box 204)
  - Invoices, 1870-1872 (Box 205)
  - Invoices, 1872-1874 (Box 206)
  - Invoices, 1875-1877 (Box 207)
  - Invoices, 1878-1879 (Box 208)
  - Invoices, 1879 (Box 209)
  - Invoices, 1879-1880 (Box 210)
  - Invoices, 1880-1881 (Box 211)
  - Invoices, 1882-1883 (Box 212)
  - Invoices, 1883 (Box 213)
  - Invoices, 1883-1884 (Box 214,)
  - Invoices, 1884-1886 (Box 215)
  - Invoices, 1886-1887 (Box 216)
  - Invoices, 1887-1889 (Box 217)
  - Invoices, 1889-1891 (Box 218)
  - Invoices, 1891-1895 (Box 219)
  - Invoices, 1895-1897 (Box 220)
  - Invoices, 1898 (Box 221)
  - Invoices, 1899-1903 (Box 222)
  - Invoices, 1903-1904 (Box 223)
  - Invoices, 1904-1906 (Box 224)
  - Invoices, 1906-1908 (Box 225)
  - Vouchers, 1885-1887 (Box 226)
  - Pay day cash book, 1887-1892 (Box 227)
- SERIES D. RECORDS OF ADDITIONAL COMPANIES AND MISCELLANEOUS VOLUMES IN THE TAYLOR COLLECTION, 1872-1893
  - RELIEF HILL
    - Daybook, Oct 1882-July 1383 (Box 227)
    - Daybook, July 1883-April 1884 (Box 227)
    - Daybook, April-Dec 1884 (Box 227)
    - Daybook, Dec 1884-Sept 1885 (Box 227)
    - Daybook, Sept 1885-July 1886 (Box 227)
    - Daybook, July 1886-June 1887 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, June-Nov 1887 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, Nov-Dec 1887 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, Dec 1887-Jan 1888 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, Feb-Aug 1888 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, Aug 1888-June 1889 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, June 1889-Jan 1890 (Box 228)
    - Daybook, April-Oct 1890 (Box 229)
    - Daybook, Oct 1890-June 1891 (Box 229)
    - Daybook, May-Sept 1893 (Box 229)
  - GOLD CANYON QUARTZ MINING COMPANY
    - Checks, 1885-1888 (Box 229)
    - Stubs, 1885-1888 (Box 229)
  - GOLD CANYON MINING COMPANY
    - Payroll, 1886-1890 (Box 229)
  - YUBA GRAVEL MINING COMPANY
    - Receipts, 1872 (Box 230)
    - Checks, 1888-1890 (Box 231)
  - MISCELLANEOUS VOLUMES
    - Expense book, 1874-1875 (Box 232)
    - Book with imprints of North Bloomfield stamp, 1883-1887 (Box 232)
    - Bar book; Union Hotel, Nevada City, 1876-1877 (Box 232)
    - Accounts, 1873-1875 (Box 232)
- SERIES E. RECORDS OF OTHER MERCANTILE ESTABLISHMENTS (APPARENTLY NOT PART OF THE TAYLOR COLLECTION), 1837-1924
  - WEAVERVILLE SUPPLY COMPANY (Weaverville, Trinity County, California)
    - Cash, 1901-1905 (Box 233)
    - Cash, 1905-1909 (Box 234)
    - Invoices, 1905-1908 (Box 235)
    - Invoices, 1909-1911 (Box 236)
  - BLAKE & REED COMPANY (Weaverville, California)
    - Daybook, 1897 (Box 236a)
    - Daybook, 1901 (Box 236b)
    - Bills, 1896-1897 (Box 236c)
    - Cash, 1909-1918 (Box 236)
    - Ledger, 1898-1900 (Box 237)
    - Invoices, 1895-1898 (Box 238)
    - Invoices, 1898-1900 (Box 239)
  - McNEAR & BROS.
    - Journal, 1871-1875 (Box 240)
    - Cash, 1864-1869 (Box 241)
    - Ledger, 1867-1869 (Box 242)
  - DOLLEY'S STORE (Sierraville, California)
    - Journal, June 1892-Sept 1892 (Box 243)
    - Journal, Sept-Dec 1892 (Box 243)
    - Journal, June-Dec 1893 (Box 243)
    - Daybook, Oct 1890-April 1891 (Box 243)
    - Daybook, May 1891-June 1892 (Box 243)
    - Daybook, Sept-Nov 1891 (Box 244)
    - Daybook, Nov 1891-Feb 1892 (Box 245)
    - Daybook, Jan 1893-July 1893 (Box 246)
  - WEATHERBEE AND COOK (Lumber dealers, San Francisco)
    - Daybook, 1862-1866 (Box 247)
    - Account book, 1860-1862 (Box 243)
    - Township book of timber -purchases in Northern California, 1883-1886 (Box 249)
  - CHYSOPOLIS COMPANY
    - Receipts, n.d. (Box 250)
  - FRAZER & COMPANY (Palo Alto, California)
    - Journal, 1919-1921 (Box 251)
    - Journal, 1922-1924 (Box 252)
    - Journal, 1922-1924 (Box 253)
    - Cash, 1913-1914 (Box 254)
    - Cash, 1927-1928 (Box 254a)
    - Cash, 1928-1929 (Box 255)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1907-1908 (Box 256)
  - W. WILLIAMS
    - Account book, 1837-1840 (Box 257)
  - J. SORROUS (Grandson still runs a general store in Sutter Creek, according to a card enclosed in the volume, of an undetermined date)
    - Journal, 1871-1872 (Box 258)
- SERIES F. MISCELLANEOUS BUSINESS RECORDS, 1865-1938
  - Journal, 1873-1875 (Box 259)
  - Journal, 1878-1880 (Box 260)
  - Journal, 1934-1938 (Box 261)
  - Journal, 1936 (Box 262)
  - Daybook: Globe Mine, 1908-1011 (Box 263)
  - Daybook, March-July 1895 (Box 264)
  - Daybook, July-Dec 1895 (Box 265)
  - Daybook, April-Oct 1896 (Box 266)
  - Daybook, Sept 1897-April 1898 (Box 267)
  - Daybook, Oct 1902-April 1903 (Box 268)
  - Daybook, July-Oct 1904 (Box 269)
  - Daybook, Sept 1905-Jan 1906 (Box 270)
  - Daybook, April-July 1908 (Box 271)
  - Daybook, July-Sept 1908 (Box 272)
  - Daybook, Sept-Dec 1908 (Box 273)
  - Daybook, June-Sept l909 (Box 274)
  - Daybook, Nov 1909-March 1910 (Box 275)
  - Daybook, June-Aug 1910 (Box 276)
  - Daybook, Nov 1910-Feb 1911 (Box 277)
  - Daybook, 1932 (Box 278)
  - Daybook, 1933 (Box 279)
  - Cash, 1894-1901 (Box 280)
  - Cash, 1896-1897 (Box 280)
  - Cash, 1897-1900 (Box 280)
  - Cash, 1899-1908 (Box 280)
  - Receipts and disbursements, 1912 (Box 280a)
  - Order book, 1937-1938 (Box 281)
  - Grocery inventory, 1938 (Box 281)
  - Record book, 1934-1937 (Box 281)
  - Ledger, n.d. (Box 281)
  - David Craig; Monkton Parish School-exercise book in business records, 1865 (Box 281)
  - Index no date, or indication to which ledger it belongs. (Box 281)
  - Index to ledger No. 1 of the A.D. Company (Box 282)
  - Ledger, 1905 (Box 282a)
  - Ledger, 1912 (Box 282b)
  - Order ledger, n.d. (Box 283)
  - Index, distribution book, 1906-1907 (Box 284)
  - Index, distribution book, 1908-1910 (Box 285)
  - Index, distribution book, 1911-1913 (Box 286)
  - Register of deeds and leases (C.T.M.M. & L. Co.), 1889-1891 (Box 287)
  - Register of deeds and leases (C.T.M.M. & L. Co.), 1891-1907 (Box 287a)
  - Wheat register; William C. Murdoch & Co., Willows, California, 1879-1885 (Box 288)
  - Remittance register, 1889-1891 (Box 289)
  - Remittance book, Aug-Sept 1927 (Box 290)
  - Purchase record, 1924-1925 (Box 291)
  - Purchase record, 1925-1926 (Box 292)
  - Purchase record, 1926-1927 (Box 293)
  - Purchase record, 1927 (Box 294)
  - Purchase record, 1928 (Box 295)
  - Purchase record, 1929 (Box 296)
  - Purchase record, 1930 (Box 297)
  - Purchase record, 1931 (Box 298)
  - Records [Trial balance?], 1915-1921 (Box 299)
  - Records [Tral balance?], 1923-1924 (Box 300)
  - Records [Trial balance?], 1927 (Box 301)
  - Credit and money back book, 1914-1916 (Box 302)
  - Store purchases, 1918-1923 (Box 303)